{
    "subject": "resource/Devilman",
    "predicate": "ontology/magazine",
    "object": "resource/Weekly_Sh\u014dnen_Magazine",
    "human_readable": "Devilman was published in Weekly Shonen Magazine.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9003397822380066,
            "question": "In what magazine was Devilman published?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8633931875228882,
            "question": "Was Devilman serialized in a monthly or weekly magazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7529923915863037,
            "question": "What type of magazine published Devilman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7123569846153259,
            "question": "Devilman first appeared in which publication?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6092681288719177,
            "question": "Devilman's initial release was in which publication?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5903646349906921,
            "question": "What is the name of the publication that featured Devilman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5595602989196777,
            "question": "Name the magazine where Devilman made its debut."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.513849139213562,
            "question": "What is the title of the magazine that ran Devilman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33422526717185974,
            "question": "Where did Devilman first appear?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19887752830982208,
            "question": "What is the name of the periodical that hosted Devilman's story?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Devilman was published in Weekly Shonen Magazine.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5801_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Devilman first appear?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5801_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the title of the magazine that ran Devilman?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5801_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the magazine where Devilman made its debut.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5801_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5801_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5801_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5801_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5801_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5801_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5801_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5801_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5801_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5801_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5801_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple \"Devilman was published in Weekly Shonen Magazine\" because it is explicitly stated that Go Nagai began publishing Devilman as a manga in Kodansha's Weekly Sh\u014dnen Magazine, barely a month before the anime series started (document 4)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The information from the documents supports that Devilman was published in Weekly Shonen Magazine. This can be inferred from multiple sources, such as the document containing \"Devilman started serialized on Weekly Sh\u014dnen Magazine in 1972\" and details about its run in the magazine."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}